### Summary

Mobile developer with around 8 years of experience building clean and maintainable iOS software for a wide range of businesses ranging from Augmented Reality to Financial Services. Possess a strong technical background with a Masters Degree in Computer Engineering from the University of Florida. Lots of experience working in agile teams and also some independently as the only developer. Currently looking for a challenging new role and some fun people to work with. I have been living in the Netherlands for more than 5 years now and can speak Dutch as well:)

## App Showcase

Moneyou Go

Modern online mobile banking solution in NL and DE

2dehands.be

Largest Online Marketplace in Belgium

Blippar

Visual Object Recognition and Augmented Reality

Layar

World's first major Augmented Reality Platform

Jumbo

E-commerce app for Jumbo Supermarket

iPhone, iPod Touch
March 2018 - December 2018
iPhone, iPod Touch, iPad
June 2016 - December 2017
iPhone, iPod Touch, iPad
June 2015 - May 2016
iPhone, iPod Touch, iPad
November 2014 - May 2016
iPhone, iPod Touch
February 2014 - November 2014

#### Recent Work Experience

Moneyou / ABN AMRO (Financial Services)

Senior iOS Engineer - Freelance

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

March 2018 - December 2018

- Part of team doing iOS feature development and releases
- Interview new iOS Candidates
- Won moneyou hackathon and successfully implemented suggested features in the app
- Part of team creating a new and compliant banking infrastructure with AWS Serverless Lambdas

Markplaats / Ebay Inc. (Classifieds)

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

June 2016 - December 2017

Senior iOS Engineer - Freelance

- Singlehandedly maintain the 2dehands.be App for Belgium serving millions of users
- Part of the ebay global mobile team building classified apps for 11 different countries for example Gumtree UK
- Setup all required processes such as Automated Testing, Continuous Integration, Crash Analysis etc.
- Won markplaats hackathon twice consecutively
- Successfully hired and trained replacement for the role before exit

# Layar / Blippar (Augmented Reality)

Senior iOS Engineer

Amsterdam, The Netherlands November 2014 - May 2016

- Lead Developer for the iOS Layar App that makes millions of users see Augmented Reality
- Lead Developer for the iOS Layar SDK that help businesses make Augmented Reality solutions
- Part of the team building the Blippar App for visual search

### Previous Work Experience

### IceMobile Agency

Amsterdam, The Netherlands

Senior iOS Engineer February 2014 - November 2014

- Senior developer in the iOS development team building apps for the leading supermarkets in the Netherlands such as Jumbo and Albert Heijn
- Gathering business requirements and coming up with efficient technical solutions to address them
- Automating user interface testing and setting up continuous integration

Ebuddy iOS Developer Amsterdam, The Netherlands

June 2013 - January 2014

- Working in the iOS development team building the messaging app XMS that had millions of users around the world and was a competitor to watsapp

Simple Apps LLC

New Delhi, India

OwnerFebruary 2012 - June 2013

- Started an iOS App development company and built several apps under it

MicroStrategy Inc. Software Engineer

McLean, VA

September 2010 - January 2012

- Worked on several iOS development projects for the clients of Microstrategy and helped automate various tasks. Also helped develop the microstrategy SDK, iOS was a pretty new technology at this point so this was some really good experience.

Citisync.com

iOS Developer

Gainesville,FL January 2010- July 2010

- Singlehandedly built the citisync iOS Application. This was when iOS 3 was the latest version. Also my first experience as an iOS Developer and it piqued my interest in the field

Bloomberg LP

New York, NY

Financial Software Development Intern

May 2009 - August 2009

- As an intern in the manhattan office, I helped out with a number of projects in the Global Trading team writing code in C++ and managing large mainframe supercomputers

#### Education

## University of Florida

Gaineville,FL

Masters in Computer Engineering

August 2008 - August 2010

- CGPA: 3.6/4.0

#### Skills

Languages: Swift, Objective C, C, C++, Python, Bash, Javascript

**Technical Skills:** Test Driven Development, Automated UI Testing, Continuous Integration, fastlane, git, xcode, Security, Machine learning with Deep Neural Nets, Restful API Design, AWS Serverless Development

Business Skills: Agile/Scrum, Managing Expectations, Project Estimation, Converting Business Goals to Technical Requirements, Risk Management, Presentations and Demos

## Other Interests

Pilot Training, Salsa Dancing, Spanish, Hiking, Travel, Poker, Pool and Snooker